[{"answer": "And what if I don't want to give up on her", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "But you said I shouldn't call if I to give up on her", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Right", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "It sucks", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "So it's almost a retroactive decision. So I could, like, let's say, forget about her and when she comes back make like I just pretended to forget about her", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Right Wait, what do you mean", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I mean first you'll pretend not to care, not call", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Ah, see, that's the thing. Somehow they don't come back until you really don't care anymore", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Ah, see, that's the thing. Somehow they don't come back until you really don't care anymore", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "There's the rub", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " You've been through worse", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Ever since I've known you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You're right. I know", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't know about that", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Listen to you. I got an audition for a pilot at nine and I'm going. You gotta get out with some beautiful babies. You can't sit home thinking about her", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I don't know, I don't kno", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm serious. This is how you do it. I'm telling you", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Vegas! You think we'll get there by midnight", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Pirates of the fucking that place", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "This is fuckin' pos", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "That's not cool", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It doesn't matte", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What? You think she's gonna tell her pi", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Who's fucking around? I'm not making fun. Let's do it, baby", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " That's where we make our scene", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Oh, they're watching all right. They're watching", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What an asshole", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "That was so demeanin", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Did she, or did she not smile", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "She was smiling at how I am, baby", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Leave? The hone", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I she's coming back", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Are you ready to order", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "That's right", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "were a rebound, and we lasted six years", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "It's a rebound", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yeah, but how long was the relationship she was rebounding ", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Baby, you're so money you don't even know it", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "my friend went for you, right", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What? Like, you didn't want to jinx it", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "against the ", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "They're a bitch team! ", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I wish the game still had fights so I could bitc", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "No. Doesn't that suck", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I don't know. I guess kids were hitting each other or something", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "YeahIf you hit them hard their heads bleed all over the ice and their legs convulse", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I can't wait till I actually get to touch one of them", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "There's the rub", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Oh. You know", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "No, man. I know you didn't get it 'cause you wouldn't've asked me. It wasn't that funny anywa", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sorry. How'd your folks take it", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "You haven't told then, huh", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "You asked her for her number, and then you tore it up", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "That doesn't matter", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "double diamon", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "True", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "What's that like", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " I know! that place! I served you an espresso at that place", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " Well, thank you...", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Thank you, my friend", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Baby, don't talk that way, bab", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "That's what I keep trying to tell him.  You're so money, you don't even kno", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "we're no", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "and big fuckin' teet", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "And you're just looking at your claws like", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Yeah. You're just gently batting it aroundand the rabbit's all scare", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Hey, man, you're not here. You don't know how it is. I in L.A", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Whatever. Things are different here. It's not like that place, my friend", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "How am I doing well? I host an open mike and I played a fuckin' bus driver in a movie. Big fuckin' deal. I'm with an agency that specializes in fuckin magicians. How good am I doing", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "They turned you down", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "Hi, my friend. I'm my friend", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Hi, my friend. I'm my friend", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": " Yes. Like the quiche", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Like the quiche", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "I like quiche", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yes. I mean, no. I mean, maybe he would find her, I mean you attractive. Maybe he doesn't like to dance. Maybe all he likes to do is just stand around and drink and smoke and look cool with his buddies who don't dance eithe", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": " NoMaybe that's not the case. Maybe she shouldn't be such a smug little shit because she'd be surprised at what a good dancer he really is, but it's been a long time and he doesn't know if he's ready t", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, I should be gettin", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "home. It's getting late. Yeah", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Good.  I think about things", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "I miss you, my friend", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "I couldn't. Do you know how hard it's been not to call you? I pick up the phone every night. Whenever that commercial comes o", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Swingers.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 90}]